Yes, we get Superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
We're living in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on.
Till we see the light, the sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know, that's
what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers!
Superpowers!
Allies, get your asses in here
till we come up with something!
Come on, let's go!
We get to go in?
Fire tank pirates, provide cover!
Lili!
Hey, Veggie!
Veggie, I saw it with my own eyes.
You were plotting to
assassinate Mama, weren't you?
How long has she been planning
this from the beginning?
Get inside the castle, Lili!
Okay, look! Cannon! Preparation!
Cannon firing, baby!
Even cooler!
No way!
It's a robot cancer!
There's no time to be excited!
I don't know how long we
can hold out like this.
Oh gee?
There it is.
Meet it, the hell is that?
Who dares to mess with the
great gangster, Castino?
He's gonna kill me!
Katakuri, thank you.
Let's go.
Not so fast.
Governor, don't be slow, Leno.
I'll juice you to death!
Nami!
You're not gonna get past us!
Oh, yes! That's hot!
Let's go!
I got you now! Oh, no!
Let's go, bro!
Gee!
Let's go.
Unite!
Gemma double six, let's go!
Let's go.
Get him! Fire!
Burn like the trash you are!
I see why mama wanted their technology.
Cheap memory armor, is it?
Lickety looks like it's
flame-proof, too. No matter.
I'll use my candy to
immobilize them once again.
And away!
All who face our scientific
might will kneel.
You fleas are nothing to me.
What have you got in
there, a bunch of hot air?
It sure as hell ain't muscle!
Aaaahhh!
I've got you!
Are you guys okay?
Nice catch!
It's my pleasure, I assure you.
You're ready for this!
Go, go, ship! Fire! Murphy!
Quickly now!
This way!
Time to pack it up, little-littles!
Well, well, well!
Looks like it's just
you and me, Tomate Box,
and thanks to all this chaos,
I get a private showing.
Everyone else will be none the wiser.
Let's take a little peek and see
what secrets you've got in there!
Oh, my God.
She's still squawking.
We got one more shot to
bump off the old Betty.
It ain't over yet.
Cannon firing.
No good.
Candy wall.
Peril Sparrow.
That one hurt.
You're colluding with Gemma, I see.
Cuckoo, you deserve
whatever is coming to you!
Yeah, yeah, laugh it up, bozo.
Look, movement!
I'll keep blastin' it
till I run out of ammo.
Hey, Mom, see you on here!
Cannon!
Firing!
What happened?
Hey, fire it up!
All the cannons on the left
wall have been destroyed!
Looks like every last one of
them is jammed with mochi!
If we fire, they'll blow!
I got an announcement, so make
sure you guys can hear it.
The Big Father's treads
are trapped in candy.
Andy, that means we ain't going nowhere.
Even worse, we're surrounded on all
sides by Big Mom's whole family.
We've got no other choice but to hold
ourselves up and wait for the inevitable.
We were so close.
If everyone steps out,
we'll give them a licking.
You're just delaying the endeavor.
How could you let them
use your power like that?
I'm the victim here.
I didn't want to help them.
Let's just kick their asses
and put this behind us, huh?
Poison, huh?
That might be a problem.
Hey, you're back!
I'm so jealous!
I wish I could turn into a giant castle!
Your devil food is so cool!
Wipe that grin off your face.
We're in a bad spot right now.
We've been planning that
assassination for a stinking year,
and the whole damn thing
blew up on our faces.
I've never failed at a hit job in my life.
Must be losing my touch.
I suppose an emperor may be
out of our league, after all.
What should we do now?
Whatever it is, we better do it quick,
because we won't be safe in here for long.
All right, get your heads
on straight and listen up.
This castle still meets.
It's strong, but not unbreakable.
If it gets busted up, then I die.
And that means nowhere for you to hide.
In other words, you're gonna be dinner for
all those sharks we got circling outside.
It's dinner!
They won't get away with this!
Mama?
Her anger is bubbling up and boiling over.
You're damned if you leave, but
you're damned if you stay in here too.
We're in dire straits.
Don't blame it on me, Benji.
That launcher was the world's
most state-of-the-art.
What happened? You okay?
Hey, Benji, you with us?
Talk to me, honey.
It can't be.
Outside.
You little rat.
Stop hiding!
Where is Benji?
And Straw Hat?
That's creepy!
She's looking right at me!
Well, crap.
So she came to her senses, huh?
all of you come out of that castle
stop cowering and face me Ah!
Ah!
Hang in there!
Time to pay the price
for betraying me, Benji!
Right now!
No!
Don't die!
You ruined my tea party! You pay!
Buggy!
Hold on, the pass!
Think you can't run?
Come on! Wait!
Look, it's me, Mama!
Beggy's my husband, and we have
a child together, you remember?
Forgive him!
Siobhan!
You dare to beg me with Lola's face?
She's coming!
Race yourself!
Get back, Chiffon! Get down! Please! Mama!
Your ugly mug is the last
thing I want to see right now!
That was a close one.
Are you OK?
OK!
Were you in on this assassination
plot, Chiffon? Traitor!
You won't live to eat
another bite of sweets!
Mama!
She'll destroy the castle in Veggie.
When he dies, all the others
will be thrown out here.
Don't let a single one of them escape.
So it's the fire tank pirates, huh?
And some of the Straw Hats.
They've got Jinbei as well.
And Germa Double Six.
All of them are responsible
for ruining the tea party.
They thought they could
get away with this?
What a joke.
Let's teach them all a lesson
for the whole world to see.
I'm out!
Benji! Here.
Honey!
Are you okay?
Damn, that stinkin' hag.
I could take cannon
fire without a scratch,
but she's banging up the big fodder
like my arm is made of cardboard!
I'm gonna go out there and kick her ass!
There's no other way!
Luffy, no!
Chopper, go stop him! I'm on it!
Let go!
Hey, what's the deal?
Chopper, I gotta go fight! Calm down!
You don't need to risk your life for this!
We came here to take back Sanji,
and that is exactly what we did.
Not only that, we got a copy of the
Poneglyph and rescued Sanji's family,
just like he asked us to.
Don't throw away everything
we've accomplished so far!
If you have enough time to fight back,
then why don't you think about
how we can escape instead?
If we'd come here to fight,
then we would have brought Zoro and
Franky and everyone else, right?
Luffy, it's just as Nami says.
We were fortunate to have made it this
far, and we owe that to our small numbers.
The others are waiting.
We must make it to the
land of Wano safely.
Ah, Page!
That's not good. Oh, no!
Chumper, let go!
Look, we can't just leave him like that.
Benji's going through all this pain
because he's trying to protect us.
Damn it all.
My plan is in shambles over here.
I'm not going to stand by and listen
to you brag about all your success.
Does that mean you're
going to throw us out?
There's no need to take us down with you.
I did my job just like you told me to.
Give me back my heart.
Take you down, huh?
Ain't a bad idea. Huh?
Not like I have any particular
fondness for you mugs.
Thing is, we're in this together,
and I care about my men so much.
I love my wife and child so much;
there's no way in hell
I'm letting them die here!
Honey!
Father!
Benji!
If we want everyone in here to survive,
there's only one answer.
You have a plan?
What is it?
if you don't get out there
then i'm gonna destroy you.
it's only a matter of time now,
get ready to bust them up the
second they come out of there.
i can't escape now—show no
mercy, kill every last one!
don't
keep a lady waiting because i think
i'm due for some sweet revenge.
okay,
so here's how it goes: the big fodder
looks like a castle but it's still me.
so this room is actually inside my body.
hey,
don't freak out on me kid!
No
matter how much I get roughed up outside.
Even
if the big fodder gets
knocked over flat on its back.
The
rest of you won't get hurt
or even shaken around.
In
other words, as long as I don't bite
the big one, you guys are safe in here.
I hadn't noticed.
Only Veggie has been
affected by the attack.
You
can hear Big Mom pounding
her fists against the walls.
But
it's perfectly calm in here.
You're
starting to get it now.
And even if I change back into my human
form, the inside is still unaffected.
Listen, I'll change back from my
castle form, keeping all I is inside.
Then Caesar will carry me
and fly away to escape.
If
we can make it to the shore,
we'll blow this popsicle!
popsicle
Hey!
Why do I have to risk my life out
there while everybody else stays safe?
And this plan is a suicide
mission, by the way.
We'll get riddled with bullets the
second those maniacs lay eyes on us.
This plan has a less than
0 % chance of success.
Even turning into gas won't help.
They'll just use their stinking
armament Haki to take me out.
Answer me one thing.
Sanji.
Why did you save us?
We fell into that trap on our own,
and we are hardly your allies.
Because my father would be
disappointed in me, that's why.
I used to hold on to all the
resentment from so many years ago.
Why did I do wrong, Dad?
Let me out!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry that I was supposed to leave!
Please, help me!
I can't live in here by myself!
If I'd grown up to be such
a small-minded man that
I would laugh at the death
of my own flesh and blood,
I couldn't face him.
Take care.
Don't catch cold.
If I can't stand tall and look my
father in the eye, then I've failed him.
No matter what, if anyone
ever asks about your family,
you must never tell
them who your father is.
Having you as a son is my greatest shame.
You must know that.
Thirteen years ago,
Vinsmoke Sanji escaped from the
Kingdom of Germa and died at sea.
You got exactly what you wanted.
After this, we're done!
You're not my father, Finn Smoke
Judge, and don't you forget that.
After this, I don't ever
want to see your face again!
I understand.
You have my word.
This is the last you'll see of me.
And I'll stay away from
the East Blue as well.
Would you stop relying on me for help?
I fulfilled my part of the bargain!
If you don't help us, then
you die too! Jesus! Huh?
Open the castle gate!
Hear my words, Peggy.
Until Caesar delivers
you safely from here,
Germa double six will act as your guards.
What? No!
You don't get to volunteer me!
I didn't agree to this!
You're acting all noble, but
you're as arrogant as ever!
I forgot.
You Germa people can fly too, can't you?
So we can leave without yous? Certainly.
Good!
If we're buying time, then I'll help too!
It's alright, Luffy. You sure?
I don't want to be indebted
to that failure any longer.
This is his way of making amends.
Hey, don't get ahead of yourselves.
I still haven't agreed to this, you know.
Stop whining.
Just do it.
Don't pay for me!
You can't hide from me, Bimsy!
Jennifer, don't hold anything back!